<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fund-raisings on Pittsburgh Curling Club</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/</link><description>Recent content in Fund-raisings on Pittsburgh Curling Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 17:16:43 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amazon Smile</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/amazon-smile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 17:16:43 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/amazon-smile/</guid><description> Another way to make a difference If you shop at amazon.com you can make a difference. Sign up for smile.amazon.com and Amazon donates a portion of your purchases to the Pittsburgh Curling Club. Once you sign up be sure to access Amazon through https://smile.amazon.com to make your purchases count. Click on the “get started” button to the right to, well… get started.</description></item><item><title>Giant Eagle Giftcards</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/giant-eagle-giftcards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 17:12:21 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/giant-eagle-giftcards/</guid><description> Giant Eagle Giftcards</description></item><item><title>Online Donation</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/online-donation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 16:47:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/online-donation/</guid><description>Help support the Pittsburgh Curling Club Donate $75 or more and we'll send you a Building Sponsor pin. If you would like a pin be sure to NOT donate anonymously. Please keep your email donation receipt as your official tax record. EIN: 76-0707291 Your donation will be processed securely by donate.ly. The official registration and financial information of the Pittsburgh Curling Club may be obtained from the Pennsylvania Department of State by calling toll-free, within Pennsylvania, 1-800-732-0999.</description></item><item><title>Fund Raising</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/donations/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 16:35:22 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/donations/</guid><description>Donations The Pittsburgh Curling Club is a 501(c)(3) charitable organization.
If you make a donation to the Pittsburgh Curling Club, you will receive a letter acknowledging the amount of your donation for tax purposes.
Donations may be mailed to:
Pittsburgh Curling Club PO Box 515 Moon Township, PA 15108 Checks only please, made out to Pittsburgh Curling Club
Alternatively, you can give online on this page.
The official registration and financial information of the Pittsburgh Curling Club may be obtained from the Pennsylvania Department of State by calling toll-free, within Pennsylvania, 1-800-732-0999.</description></item></channel></rss>