<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pittsburgh Curling Club</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/</link><description>Recent content on Pittsburgh Curling Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 17:16:43 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://curlpgh.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amazon Smile</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/amazon-smile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 17:16:43 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/amazon-smile/</guid><description> Another way to make a difference If you shop at amazon.com you can make a difference. Sign up for smile.amazon.com and Amazon donates a portion of your purchases to the Pittsburgh Curling Club. Once you sign up be sure to access Amazon through https://smile.amazon.com to make your purchases count. Click on the “get started” button to the right to, well… get started.</description></item><item><title>Giant Eagle Giftcards</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/giant-eagle-giftcards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 17:12:21 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/giant-eagle-giftcards/</guid><description> Giant Eagle Giftcards</description></item><item><title>Online Donation</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/online-donation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 16:47:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/online-donation/</guid><description>Help support the Pittsburgh Curling Club Donate $75 or more and we'll send you a Building Sponsor pin. If you would like a pin be sure to NOT donate anonymously. Please keep your email donation receipt as your official tax record. EIN: 76-0707291 Your donation will be processed securely by donate.ly. The official registration and financial information of the Pittsburgh Curling Club may be obtained from the Pennsylvania Department of State by calling toll-free, within Pennsylvania, 1-800-732-0999.</description></item><item><title>2020 2021 Registration</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/members/2020-2021-registration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 15:38:20 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/members/2020-2021-registration/</guid><description>Pittsburgh Curling Club Registration Use the button below to register for the Spring/Summer 2021 session. This session will start on April 19th, 2021 and ends on August 29, 2021. Members can participate in the number of draws that their selected plan provides. Any unused draws expire after August 29, 2021. The Pittsburgh Curling Club COVID-19 protocols remain in place for the 2021 Spring/Summer session. It is our intent to continue to operate safely under these guidelines until the pandemic abates.</description></item><item><title>Calendar</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/members/calendar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 15:37:43 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/members/calendar/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Scheduling</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/members/scheduling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 15:37:22 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/members/scheduling/</guid><description>Scheduling Contact scheduling with questions regarding the 2020/21 curling season at our new facility in Stowe Township.
scheduling@pittsburghcurlingclub.com</description></item><item><title>Learn to Curl</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/learn-to-curl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 06:46:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/learn-to-curl/</guid><description>Do I need any equipment? No! We have all the equipment you need to learn to curl. Just be sure to wear warm, comfortable clothing -track pants or sweatpants work best, and athletic rubber soled shoes such as tennis shoes. You’ll be good to go!! Is curling hard to do? Curling is easy to learn and fun to play right from the first stone you throw. Most everyone we meet has seen curling televised at the Winter Olympics – looks easy, right?</description></item><item><title>Phased Reopening Plan</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/covid/phased-reopening-plan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 06:30:11 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/covid/phased-reopening-plan/</guid><description>The Pittsburgh Curling Club will begin a phased reopening plan for our club starting on Saturday June 13, 2020.
For more information regarding our COVID preparedness, please contact Dr. Minnie Meals at minnie.meals@pittsburghcurlingclub.com
For general inqueries, please contact info@pittsburghcurlingclub.com</description></item><item><title>Covid Reponse Plan</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/covid/covid-response-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 16:38:48 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/covid/covid-response-plan/</guid><description>Below is an outline of the Pittsburgh Curling Club’s response plan for members who may be at risk for COVID.
Guidelines for Responding to Symptomatic Individuals The following is a general response for members of Pittsburgh Curling Club or visitors who exhibit symptoms of COVID-19, including fever, persistent coughing, and/or shortness of breath.
If you have or think you may have symptoms of COVID-19 If currently on PCC premises, the symptomatic individual must go home immediately.</description></item><item><title>Fund Raising</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/donations/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 16:35:22 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/fund-raising/donations/</guid><description>Donations The Pittsburgh Curling Club is a 501(c)(3) charitable organization.
If you make a donation to the Pittsburgh Curling Club, you will receive a letter acknowledging the amount of your donation for tax purposes.
Donations may be mailed to:
Pittsburgh Curling Club PO Box 515 Moon Township, PA 15108 Checks only please, made out to Pittsburgh Curling Club
Alternatively, you can give online on this page.
The official registration and financial information of the Pittsburgh Curling Club may be obtained from the Pennsylvania Department of State by calling toll-free, within Pennsylvania, 1-800-732-0999.</description></item><item><title>Group Events</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/group-events/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 16:35:10 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/group-events/</guid><description>Group Events The Pittsburgh Curling Club can provide a unique learn to curl experience for your group.
In a 2 hour session we’ll teach you how to deliver the rock, sweep, explain basic strategy, and allow your group to play a short game.
Contact us at scheduling@pittsburghcurlingclub.com and we will provide details.</description></item><item><title>Members</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/members/current-draw-info/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 16:35:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/members/current-draw-info/</guid><description>Current Draws Draw times and Draw-masters Spring/Summer, Session beginning April 19th and ending August 29th 2021. Sunday Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday Friday Saturday Time 3:30pm - 5:30pm Format Open Draw Drawmaster Karyn Drombosky - Time 6pm-8pm 7pm-9pm 7pm-9pm 7pm-9pm 4pm-6pm Format Doubles Open Draw Open Draw Open Draw Open Draw Drawmaster Sean Mizerski Ryan Waskiewicz Mark Robinson Burt Cubison Steve Buffington These are initial draw offerings, additional draws and times may be added as demand develops.</description></item><item><title>Waiver</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/about/waiver/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 11:48:20 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/about/waiver/</guid><description>Waiver The waiver can be downloaded here.
Please print it out, complete it, and bring it with you to curling.</description></item><item><title>Bylaws Policies</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/about/bylaws-policies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 11:04:40 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/about/bylaws-policies/</guid><description>Bylaws Pittsburgh Curling Club Bylaws (2012)
Policies Team eligibility for events with limited entries per curling club
SafeSport The Pittsburgh Curling club has adopted the USCA recommended, SafeSport policies
SafeSport</description></item><item><title>Board Meetings</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/about/board-meetings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 10:41:26 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/about/board-meetings/</guid><description>Board Meetings 2021 Board meetings are currently held on the second Tuesday of each month at 7:30 PM in the warm room at the Pittsburgh Curling Club:
491 McCoy Road McKees Rocks, PA 15136 Google Map
All members are welcome and encouraged to attend! We hope to see you there!</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/about/contact/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 09:54:55 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/about/contact/</guid><description>Contact General Information
info@pittsburghcurlingclub.com
We are located at:
Pittsburgh Curling Club 491 McCoy Road McKees Rocks, PA 15136 Google Map
Executive Committee President: Dustin Devine dustin.devine@pittsburghcurlingclub.com
Vice President: Mark Robinson mark.robinson@pittsburghcurlingclub.com
Treasurer: Daphne Roberts daphne.roberts@pittsburghcurlingclub.com
Secretary: Karyn Drombosky karyn.drombosky@pittsburghcurlingclub.com
Board of Directors
Steve Buffington steve.buffington@pittsburghcurlingclub.com
Nick Connolly nick.connolly@pittsburghcurlingclub.com
Burt Cubbison burt.cubbison@pittsburghcurlingclub.com
Travis Eiler travis.eiler@pittsburghcurlingclub.com
Len Jarabeck leonard.jarabeck@pittsburghcurlingclub.com
Marie Rose marie.rose@pittsburghcurlingclub.com</description></item><item><title>Board</title><link>https://curlpgh.org/about/board/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 09:40:30 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://curlpgh.org/about/board/</guid><description>Officers and Directors President — Dustin Devine
Vice President — Mark Robinson
Secretary — Travis Eiler
Treasurer — Daphne Roberts
Directors serving until 2022
Burt Cubbison, Daphne Roberts, Mark Robinson, Marie Rose
Directors serving to 2023
Steve Buffington, Nick Connolly, Dustin Devine, Travis Eiler
Directors serving until 2024
Len Jarabeck, Erin McManus, Sean Mizerski, Deb Spang</description></item></channel></rss>